Hello, I'm your host, David Bernard, and
my guest today is Ashley Black. After 6
years leading the app ads team at
Google, Ashley left Google to found
Candid Consulting, an agency that helps
apps run effective marketing campaigns
for Android and iOS.
On the podcast, I talked with Ashley
about what makes Google app campaigns so
effective for growth, proven
optimization strategies, and why lower
CPMs can sometimes be a warning sign
rather than a win.
Hey Ashley, thanks so much for joining
me on the podcast today. Happy to see
you again. So, we're going to be talking
about Google app campaigns today, and I
wanted to kick things off with your
experience, cuz you do have a kind of
unique perspective compared to a lot of
folks that we talked to on the podcast.
So, why don't why don't you share what
you've been doing the past 10 years, and
then what you're doing now? Yeah, so I
think there's a lot of like, you know,
UA experts out there, and and a lot of
people obviously who work in apps. I
guess my specialty lies within Google
app campaigns, their ads product. For
the last year I've been out on my own,
but prior to that I spent 9 and 1/2
years working at Google. Six of those
years I led the app ads sales team. So,
my team worked directly mostly with game
developers, or the marketing teams
within those games. So, I guess I have a
lot more insight knowledge as to like
the the product and how things actually
work. So, my perspective tends to be a
little bit more unique. It's really cool
that you were in Google for so long, and
then you know, kind of a little bit of a
backstory that you've told me and shared
publicly is that it was frustrating at
times to work with customers where you
kind of knew certain things that they
could maybe be helpful, but weren't
really appropriate for you to share as
somebody working at Google. And so, you
did start a consulting company where you
can say those things and maybe even be
more directly helpful to to the
customers.
Yeah, I think one of the things that
this happens at any large company,
right? Where you feel that there's a lot
of processes that you have to go through
in order to actually be able to say
anything, or there has to be so much
data that's collected in order for
Google to say, "Okay, this is how we can
position this product." And I always
felt really stifled by that, cuz I'm
like, "People just want to know." And
And I think you guys understand better
than anybody, people want to test
things, too. So, for us to have to wait
years in some cases to be able to
communicate to people what we feel like
maybe we already know, but you know,
product or legal hasn't given us the
stamp of approval to do so, I found to
always be like really infuriating. So,
now I I sort of offer a lot of those hot
takes that I wasn't allowed to do
before, but always with a grain of salt,
like, you know, it's testing at the end
of the day, but yes, I do have I've seen
thousands and thousands of these
accounts, and so I I probably have a
little bit more credibility when I make
these statements. Yeah, I was just
talking to Shrina, who was actually the
the very last episode. So, for those of
you who didn't listen, go back and
listen to that one. One of the things we
talked about quite a bit in that episode
was how important it is to take risks,
and how important it is to foster a
culture of taking risks
when you're doing user acquisition and
trying ads, because you have to take
some risk, you have to try some new
things, you have to kind of go out on a
limb
in order to find those things that are
going to, you know, double your
performance. And that's one thing she
talked about, was like they were able to
double their performance over the course
of a few years through like hundreds of
tests.
And so, it's kind of cool to hear that.
It's like, when you're at Google, you
can't it's hard to tell people to take a
risk, it may lose them tens of thousands
of dollars. Like, that's not what Google
wants to do, they want to only share the
like tried and true strategies. And so,
yeah, it's it's interesting to hear that
that one of the bigger frustrations was
that you couldn't help people take those
kind of risks, but it's those kind of
risks that get you that like, you really
do optimize your performance over time.
I think one of the things that I felt
most passionate about, and it's really
how Candid Consulting came to be, was on
the iOS front, where Google Google has a
very
complicated relationship with Apple. And
so, we were so limited on what we were
able to say when it wasn't regards to
SKAdNetwork and how Google's model was
working and and what we were rolling
out. And I would always advocate
internally when I was there to say,
like, "Hey, people just need some bit of
information. I know that we can't, you
know, say definitively this is what
we're doing, or we may have to pivot
later based on what Apple changes, and
and people I think understand that. What
people don't like is silence. And that's
what I was really frustrated by a lot of
times, was just the silence because
there was all of this, you know,
back-end complications that honestly I
didn't always have visibility into. They
were happening I think a lot of times
with like the engineers and the product
teams and people very high up. But yeah,
it was like, "People just want to know
something. Like, can't we just tell them
something?" Cuz like, I can tell them
little things, but it was like, "No, no,
no, not yet." And so, leaving has
obviously enabled me to be able to share
those insights. Let's just kick things
off from the highest level overview then
of like, what is Google app campaigns,
and you know, why should this audience
of subscription app growth practitioners
generally, and I mean we have indie
developers and CEOs and kind of a broad
audience of folks who are going to be
listening to this, but like, why should
people be thinking about, care about, or
what should they know about Google app
campaigns? If you have an app and you're
starting to think about how you actually
pay to get users to download that app,
you're probably going to start looking
at Google. Although, I find a lot of
people start with Meta first, or if
they're heavy on iOS, they'll start with
start with Apple search ads, but
typically Google is first or second
when they're looking to explore. So,
Google app campaigns, if we take the,
you know, the history of it, I'm going
to say it was probably 8 years ago now,
maybe nine, where Google actually this
was their first machine learning ads
product. And it was very novel because
people Well, people did not like the
idea that Google was taking all of this
control. They were basically saying,
"Tell us how much you want to spend on a
daily basis. Tell us how much you're
willing to pay for whatever it is." An
install, I think at the time it was
mostly just installs, but now it can be
how much you're willing to pay for a
subscriber, somebody to start trial. And
throw in some creative, and we got it
from here. You don't need to tell us
anything else. And And that's What's
interesting is that's the direction
Google has moved with a lot of its
products.
And I'm not as familiar on like the
website of things, but people talk about
PMax, and I think you're starting to see
an expansion of this. And the reason why
is like, it works. It really does. Like,
at the at the time, Google's app ads
product contributed nothing. And by
large, in comparison to search, it's
still a very small percentage of their
ads revenue, but it has grown massively,
and so the product does really work. So,
it started out as UAC, Universal App
Campaigns. That's what most people call
it, because it's easy, everybody loves
an acronym. They dropped the U a couple
years ago, so it is just app campaigns.
Basically, it allows you to serve across
all different inventory types, but you
don't have control over where Well, you
kind of don't have control over where
your ad serves. So,
get into some of the fun little hacks to
to get a little more control. That was
one of the frustrations when UAC came
out, was that it limited so much
control, but that trade-off was the
performance, you know? We see Meta going
that direction as well. I'm giving you
less specific control, but then the
algorithms have just gotten so good both
at Google, Meta, and other ad products,
where the algorithm is going to end up
making better decisions, and that's why
they did it. So, what what would you say
are some of the key benefits then of
Google app campaigns, and then we can
get to some of the drawbacks that And
we've already kind of discussed some of
them. Whenever I talk about Google, you
really have to talk about it for Android
and for iOS. I feel like with Meta,
people they don't really care too much,
or people don't I don't notice people,
you know, sort of like separating the
two and talking about them separately,
but I feel with app campaigns, or I'll
just say UAC,
it is really critical because on
Android, you have the benefit of
actually serving your ads in the Play
Store. That's like super high intent.
You cannot get that inventory anywhere
else, right? So, that just doesn't
exist. You can't buy it, it's not like
part of another network. So, I think
that's really the main advantage of UAC
when it comes to Android.
And also, there's a lot of other
properties, right? You have Google
search and YouTube. So, there there's a
lot more that you can leverage there,
too, but by and far, the Play Store's
huge. On iOS, yeah, like Google's
actually not as competitive, but I
really don't feel it can be overlooked.
You still have Google search, which
again, you can't buy search from
anywhere else, and you have YouTube,
which still is like the number one app.
It's like the most downloaded app in the
world, I think, not just in the US. So,
those two pockets of inventory are
really, you know, those are huge for you
to be able to access and be able to
advertise your app. And And you know,
this is one of the things about Meta and
why a lot of apps are finding success
right now, is that between the Facebook
app and the Instagram app, you're just
getting such broad exposure, but then
Google takes it even like multiple steps
further, like YouTube, inside the Play
Store, across search, across their
display ad networks, like it's just a
massive scale that is hard to access in
any other way. What what would you say
then are some of the the drawbacks that
that come to mind with UAC?
You know, going back to the controls,
it can be really challenging if you're
testing in particular. You you're like,
"Oh, I really want to see if how these
videos perform."
On Android, it is really challenging to
try and get your videos to get any
meaningful traffic. People can do it,
right? And it depends on the the
vertical of your app. But again, you
have the Play Store. It's going to be
really high-converting traffic. I always
liken the Play Store traffic to branded
search. Like when we would talk about,
you know, when you have your, you know,
branded keywords, right? It's like
you're reaching people at the highest
intent moment possible when they're
actually searching for something. They
want something. And that's kind of what
the Play Store is, too. They're grabbing
them right at that last minute. You
know, being able to really diversify
where your ads are showing, that can be
a big challenge. Or the opposite of
trying to force and and get traffic
somewhere else. Um getting it away like
I I was talking with a client yesterday.
All of their traffic's flowing to
display. And we're like, "How can we
force it over here?" And, you know,
aside from really paying a lot more like
manipulating your bids, which isn't
always feasible,
that can be a big drawback. And so, I
think a lot of people despise Google's
products for that reason. But as we were
kind of pointing out, it's like it's all
trade-offs. So, you trade off some of
that control for reach, for the high
intent, things like that. And we've kind
of been hitting on this already, but any
other contrast you want to paint between
UAC and the other major kind of user
acquisition channels, TikTok, Meta,
Apple Search Ads?
Oh, yeah. I I think one thing that
people look at is a lot of people are
like, "Oh, it's just a it's an app
network, right? We're using that product
to distribute our app." But you have to
think about it. If you have Let's just
use Meta as the primary example. They
have the their two main sources of
traffic are Facebook and Instagram,
right? And most of that is
app-specific. I mean, if you're doing an
app campaign, it's just going to serve
there.
On Google, we're talking about Let's
talk about like the five primary sources
of traffic that you get with your
Android campaign. You have the Play
Store.
You have Google Search, which is mostly
done in a browser. It's not like in an
app, okay? So, it's in a browser.
You have YouTube, which is probably
pretty heavy on app, but there actually
is still quite a bit of it that happens
in a browser. You have AdMob traffic,
which is
ads in other apps. That's part of
Google's network. And then you have what
they call MGIDN, which is mobile uh
Google Display Network, which is ads in
browsers, on websites, mobile websites.
So, a lot more of Google's mobile
traffic is served in browser
in comparison to these other like
app-native
platforms like a Meta or a TikTok,
right? That just like doesn't exist on
web. And so, you have to really consider
that. And that's the piece that you
really have to understand, especially
when it comes to iOS. That's why Google
I think had so many challenges for a
long time. Uh SKAdNetwork wasn't even
counting web-to-app conversions. This is
like it you know, we had cases of um
some clients where 99% of their traffic
was coming from search. And SKAN wasn't
capturing any of those conversions like
zero of them. Um now with the SKAN 4.0,
that that has changed, but there's still
a lot of limitations. And I don't know
if people realize like how unique
Google's platform is compared to some of
the other big players. And one of the
things you had shared previously, we we
did a webinar, which by the way, this
the webinar might be a good adjunct to
this if you want to go back and and
listen to Ashley's webinar, she has
slides and all that. So, kind of a nice
compliment to this conversation. But you
also mentioned Play Browse. So, so in
within the Play Store, you can actually
buy ads where if people are browsing
around looking for apps, they're going
to see those ads. Is is that serve much
traffic? And and is does that perform
well? Nobody knows, David. This is the
That's the thing That's the other reason
why people don't like this is because
you have really limited visibility into
where your ads are showing. So, in the
Google Ads like in the um front end, if
you're looking in your managing your
campaigns, you'll be able to see a
breakout of the four different inventory
sources. So, you can see they lump it as
search traffic, search network, search
partners, which usually is like a really
small percentage. If it's high, that
should be a warning sign to you. And
then there's this other one called
Google Display Network, and that's what
we'll talk about in just a sec. And then
there's YouTube.
But again, what people don't realize is
like, "What's included in those?" So, if
we're talking about search, yes, it
searches on google.com, but it's also
searches in Play. Well, you don't have a
way of seeing the breakout. If you have
a really good I tell people like if you
have a really good Google rep,
you can. They They do have the ability
to see it. They have to have the right
access, but they can show you the
breakout. So, there's google.com
searches, there's Play Search, and
that's all included in search. And then
when we talk about the Display Network,
that is the AdMob traffic a lot of
times. It's the MGIDN, which I was
talking about like website images or
ads. And then uh it also can include
Play Browse.
That's the tricky part is like you're
trying to figure out, "Okay, well, is
this not working because of this? Or is
this happening?" You're making a lot of
assumptions about things. And so, a lot
of times it can be hard because you're a
little bit blind to what's actually at
play. But overall,
the combination of all these things and
Google's algorithm that that tries to
figure out where things are going to be
performing, it does seem like overall,
it is a high-quality source of and
especially on Android, potentially very
high-intent traffic as well.
Absolutely. Even though you do have to
depend on the the algorithm to kind of
sort through, there is really
high-quality sources of traffic that are
flowing through UAC. Oh, yeah. I I don't
think that that's
that's undeniable. On Android, like we
were talking about and also on on iOS,
you have Google Search, which again,
like I just don't think people
understand is like you can't buy that
anywhere else. You can't get those types
of users who are actively querying for
product that you have anywhere else. And
so, that can't be ignored. And like you
mentioned, the sheer volume of people
like I know a lot of people You you can
get good scale on a lot of these other
platforms, but I do think a lot of those
other platforms have demographics and
audiences that they maybe skew a little
bit more toward where I feel like if you
think about Google and all the the
products that we just listed, you're
likely to find a little bit of everyone
across all of these. You know,
everybody's looking at YouTube at some
point. Everybody uses Google Search. If
you have an Android device, you're sort
of required to use the Play Store. We
don't have to get into those
requirements, but you know what I'm
saying. Just feel like it's something
that can't be ignored. And there is a
really uh
you know, high-quality user that exists
out there. You just have to put a little
bit of faith into the system that it
will find it for you. Yeah. And I think
this is a good message for the audience
that even if you're finding incredible
success on Meta and doing really well,
at some point you really should be
looking at UAC because it's going to
give you access to these sources that
are high intent and can potentially be
really well-performing ads that you just
can't get access to those people and
that traffic any other way. So, it's
like you definitely should be
considering UAC even as other networks
are performing really well.
And one thing I want to talk about, and
I think we we sort of discussed this
offline before, is I find that a lot of
people like using the other networks
because of the testing capabilities. I
mean, I feel like in my LinkedIn
influencer world of people who are into
user acquisition, there's it's a niche
group, but there seem to they seem to be
very active. There's so much
conversation around creative testing.
And people are developing like 900
videos a month to test out on Meta or on
TikTok. And nobody really talks about
Google in that in that conversation. And
so, I think sometimes people like that
control. They like the ability to test,
um which we we've talked about as well.
Like that that testing environment is
exciting. You get to see what's going to
be produced. And that doesn't exist to
the same extent on Google.
I think if you're really savvy and you
kind of know the right levers to pull or
or what sort of data to look into, you
can force some of that testing, but it's
not as obvious to be able to run, you
know, a side-by-side test between two
videos and see which resonated better
with an audience. And so, I think people
are looking for that a lot of times when
they're going to market their app. And
that can be a real challenge to do with
Google Ads. And speaking of that, you
know, the next topic I wanted to talk
about was measurement. So, how is Google
app campaigns
measuring the performance? And how
should people be thinking about that
measurement
when they start considering or start
running ads? And then we'll get into all
the tips and how to run an app
strategies and stuff like that. Sure.
So, again, this is another example where
I very distinctly call out the
difference between Android and iOS cuz
they are night and day. On Android, you
know, Google still has the
I'm going to say like GCLID or GAID. I
always forget which is which. but they
still have the ability to track at the
user level, at least for now. I know
there's things that they're rolling out,
but most of those conversions that
you're seeing in Google Ads are
deterministic, meaning like they have
confidence that those actually happened,
right? Cuz they can see that they did.
And so if you're using a platform like
an MMP to measure your performance,
generally you're going to see that the
the measurement there, what Google shows
you and what your MMP is reporting, is
pretty close. We can talk about
discrepancies, but the discrepancies are
usually a lot smaller when we're on
Android.
iOS is a whole other ballgame.
Google introduced modeled conversions.
Oh man, people hate modeled conversions.
This is Google, you know, they don't
tell anybody about it. I mean, I was
there when they rolled it all out for
iOS, and I felt like I got like nothing
from how they actually were modeling
these things. They, you know, they
talked a lot about stuff, but it wasn't
all that practical. Like I couldn't
really see understand how it was going
to roll out. But the the modeling is
Google basically saying, "Hey, we have
confidence based on all of these signals
that we have that this conversion
happened." And by the way, there's very
few deterministic conversions that
Google actually has. I'll touch on that
maybe in a little bit more detail in
just a minute. But so Google models
their conversions. Then if you were to
go into your MMP again and say, "Okay,
well, how many conversions did Google
produce?" You're going to see a huge
discrepancy.
And then when you talk about
SKAdNetwork, you're also going to see a
really enormous discrepancy there. So
Android's pretty reliable in the
measurement. iOS, we could do a whole
other podcast on it.
So is is Google using SKAdNetwork for
now? And and are they capturing those
web-to-app or I mean, the kind of dirty
secret of the the whole industry at this
point feels like is that both Meta,
Google, and everybody else doing any
kind of measurement is using the IP. And
so the quote-unquote, and for those of
you listening audio, we're both doing
like finger quotes,
modeled conversions, is probably pretty
heavily reliant on IP address
fingerprinting, which then can be fairly
confident, but then you're going to lose
some of those signals, but then
SKAdNetwork should be more
deterministic, but just in a not on a
user level. So so yeah, do do you have
any understanding of how they are and
aren't using SKAdNetwork to to help
model those conversions? Just to be
clear, on SKAdNetwork, Google, at least
I haven't heard anything changed in like
the last 6 months, does not ingest any
data from SKAdNetwork back into their
models. The only thing that they ingest
back from SKAdNetwork is the installs
that happened, nothing deeper. And I
think it is relatively complicated,
right? Like you have to figure out what
all of those conversion values mean per
each individual advertiser, right? Like
there's not like a standard set of them
to be able to say, "Okay, did this
happen?" So Google's not really using
scan in its models. Now, the
fingerprinting thing is separate. They
just announced as of recent that they
will start doing this, um the IP, I
mean. I shouldn't say fingerprinting. Um
I don't want to get in trouble, but
Oh, I know all of these big companies
are doing fingerprinting. It's a bad
word in the industry, but Google and
Apple aren't cracking I mean, Apple
specifically, especially post-ATT, is
not cracking. They say in the the they
say in all the rules like, you know,
fingerprinting is not allowed, yada
yada, but then all everybody's doing it
and and nobody's getting rejected for
it.
Yes, they they did announce that they
would be using IP as as part of it. Now,
whether they had been all along and now
they're just being forthright with it, I
don't know. So we'll we'll have to see,
but I think the one thing that I wanted
to call out because I I get calls all
the time like I do audits for a lot of
people reaching out and they're like,
"Hey, just tell me what's wrong with my
setup or we have questions." And so they
bring me on to do stuff like that. And
one of the big things that people are
confused by is the the deterministic
conversions. So this is like I always
liken it to like, you know, pre-iOS 14,
what the environment used to look like.
And again, this goes back, David, to
what I was talking about where you have
to really think about Google and all the
different inventory, like all the
different traffic sources it serves on
in comparison to some of the, you know,
the other players. So one reason why you
might see Google with like zero
conversions in your MMP deterministic
conversions or or just a fraction of
what Google is reporting or what scan
reports
is deterministic conversions can still
happen if you're able to collect the
user's IDFA, right? But again, remember,
so much of Google's traffic happens on
on browsers, on like websites. And the
opportunity to collect, you know, user
consent, the ATT prompt, right? Does not
exist on browsers. And so I think people
really overlooked that. And then
probably the biggest one, and again,
this is one of those things that I was
talking about where I wish Google had
been more vocal about it, is that they
did not prompt for it on YouTube.
And that was their biggest source of app
traffic on iOS, and they were not
collecting those users' IDFAs and for a
long time. They launched it, they
finally finally back in July of 2024
started to roll it out and actually
prompt for consent on the YouTube app.
But I noticed even still, Google does
phased rollouts of everything, right? So
they'll do like they'll launch it to
like 1% of users in one country, right?
And then they slowly and bring it out. I
didn't actually they launched that in
July. I personally didn't get the prompt
until December to opt in. Like they
hadn't even shown it to everybody. So
anyway, that that's all to say that like
Google, because of their traffic
differences and the choices that they
made, you know, back in 2021, people
don't understand like why those
decisions had a big impact on the the
measurement side of things. Yeah, yeah,
that makes a ton of sense. Well, I did
want to shift gears now. I think we, you
know, we've we've given a pretty
high-level overview of all this stuff
and gone into the weeds on different
topics, but I think what a lot of people
want to know at this point now is like,
"Okay, I'm convinced I should try UAC.
How do I do that?" And I think that the
first question most people ask is is
budget. It's like, "You know, if I want
to start spending on UAC, what does that
look like? How much do I need to spend?"
One of the things we didn't mention
earlier is that it does sometimes take
longer for UAC to for the algorithm to
to get trained. Um so sometimes it does
take higher budget. But yeah, what what
are your thoughts on like getting
started?
I'll be consistent here. I've said it
somewhere else. I know people come at me
and and say like, "Well, that didn't
work for me." And they're like, "Do I
really need to spend that much?" I'm
going to use this as if you're starting
in the US, okay? Because if we're
talking about other countries, then that
becomes much more complicated. But in
the US on Android, if you're saying
like, "What is the minimum budget I need
to start testing things?" I would say
anywhere from like two to 300 bucks a
day. Yes, you could do less and sure,
you can do more, but like if I were to
say, "Okay, you're just starting out,"
that's what I would probably want to
spend on a daily basis to get enough
information to get it fast enough to
actually be able to say, "Okay, is this
working or what adjustments do I need to
make?" On iOS, it's got to be more
significant than that. But it's also a
more expensive platform. Installs are a
lot more expensive on iOS than they are
on Android. The inventory is more
expensive. The CPMs are higher. So all
of those things need to be taken into
consideration. And so on iOS, again, I'm
just saying this as a figure, I would
say at a minimum about 500 bucks a day
to see if you can get enough traffic and
then actually have something to do with
that traffic to be able to make
adjustments as needed.
Once you start spending that and seeing
it work, how how do you then scale up
from there? What are your tips on
scaling budget? Slowly.
Slow. You don't want to like, you know,
wake the dragon or whatever it is. Um
and I I've experienced this personally
where I've always the the engineers at
Google were always like, "20%," right?
No more than 20% in any given day on
bids and budgets, up or down. And so if
you are looking to scale, I kind of got
burned not that long ago where I was
like, "I bet I could push it like a
little bit more." And then I did, and
what happens is that the system goes
goes crazy. It's like, "Woohoo! We got
it's like a 10-year-old or something
that just got more money." It's like,
"Let's go spend it. Let's go figure it
out." And it's like, "Whoa, we have to
be cautious. Let let's take, you know,
let's try and figure out new pockets of
inventory and do this in a responsible
manner." And so yeah, that 20% rule does
really apply. And I even am maybe more
conservative where I only adjust it or I
try to only adjust it by 20% every two
to three days. I try not to do it every
single day because then it just keeps
kicking it back into learning mode at
too great of a frequency. We'll dive
more into campaign management in a bit,
but with that budget, would that be on
like one campaign or can you have
multiple campaigns running at the same
time with that $500 just getting started
budget? That's one campaign.
But you really don't need more than one
campaign if you're only targeting one
geography. So if you just have one
US-based campaign, actually the guidance
is to not have a duplicate one doing the
exact same thing. There's a lot of
theories out there that like your
cannibalizing your traffic if you do
that. And that was certainly what I
think when we would submit internal
tickets sometimes and say like, "Why
isn't this working?" That's what the we
called them GTech. That was the internal
team the Google Tech team would come
back and say, "Well, it's because they
have multiple campaigns." But that was
always I think really hard to prove that
that was the case. But if you're going
to set up your campaigns, you only need
one campaign per geo.
Okay? And then if you do want to get
more granular, like you could have an a
separate one if you were doing different
bid types. Like if you're optimizing for
installs versus let's say start trials,
you would have two separate campaigns
because you do have to set your your
event optimization at the campaign
level. That's pretty rare too. I I don't
see that happening as often. Any other
tips as you're kind of ramping up? Like
if you're spending $500 a day, how long
is it going to take before the algorithm
really figures out where to show your
ads, how to show your ads?
Um any other tips on kind of ramping up?
Usually within like two to three weeks,
you can start to see how things are
going to likely trend. One other thing
that I noticed as like a mistake that a
lot of people do is they build out their
campaigns as like the bare minimum. So
they will create one campaign and then
they'll have one ad group. And the ad
group is if you're familiar with Meta is
like an ad set, right? And it's sort of
a grouping of creative that you're
testing. Now, you can't assign budgets
at the ad group level in Google. Okay?
So Google's just going to make the call
and say, "Okay, you know, we're going to
send 80% of our traffic to this one ad
group and 10% to this other one and five
to the last one and etc." So you have no
control over that. But what I always
encourage people to do is you have to
build out multiple ad groups and I I
like theme them. You know, think about
use cases and or features of your app
and then that's what I would create your
ad groups around and see what kind of
engagement you're getting on those. So
if you have a I'm just going to use like
a golf app. Maybe it's swing
performance. That's one ad group. And
then the next one is like about caddies.
That's your next one. And all of your
creative should sort of correspond to
that central theme. And then you can
kind of see what people are interacting
with. And I usually like to build out
maybe about five ad groups per campaign.
Get a little bit of traction, see what's
resonating with folks as opposed to just
doing one. If it doesn't work and then
you're like, "Well, I tried." Right?
It's like, "Well, you didn't."
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense. And And
so you already again touched on the the
next um thing I wanted to talk about and
that's creative strategy. So I know
there's like all different kind of
assets that you would put into those ad
groups. Like how do you think about
creative strategy with UAC? Like I was
saying, I I theme everything for the
most part. I think one another common
mistake that I see people make is
Google, not unlike the other platforms,
has character limits when you're
creating your text assets. Text assets
by the way are like the most crucial
part of your Google Ads campaigns.
Contrary to maybe other platforms where
people aren't even reading it, it's like
the text asset is it's just like
fundamental. And again, if you're
thinking about search, search only shows
text. All right? Search uh assets, all
right? Like that's just a text strategy.
So you got to make sure that that's
really fine-tuned.
Um and then even in the Play Store, they
will pull in your app icon and then a
bit of text that you write in the in
Google Ads. And that's what your asset
the total asset is. And so I think a lot
of people oftentimes like overlook them
or they use Google's like
recommendations to put their text
assets. And I don't know why Google
doesn't um abide by like regular
punctuation and grammar in those. But
anyway, um the text assets is really
really critical.
The other piece that I talk a lot about,
again going back to understanding what
Google's traffic is.
Thing it's really easy to see in again
like Facebook or Instagram that like,
"Oh, you always get a 15 or 20-second
reel."
Okay? And like that's what you see quite
often.
But I think on YouTube and you don't
have reporting into this, you don't
realize all the different pockets of
inventory within YouTube. So when you're
creating videos, I always tell people
probably want a 6-second video because
that's one ad format in YouTube.
You want like a 10 to 15-second video
because you know, we just want to test
out that duration. 20-second around 20
seconds is great for YouTube Shorts. 30
seconds or longer is probably going to
serve in-stream. So those are more of
those like skippable ads that you would
see if you're watching just like a
regular video. So you have to have a lot
of variety in terms of lengths on
Google. And then also the orientations.
I mostly default to portrait, especially
if we're talking about iOS. But on
Android, you can't overlook the
landscape orientation because a lot of
people still do watch their YouTube
videos, you know, in landscape mode. And
then what about image assets? Cuz So
those are the three primary assets that
you provide to Google, right? So
within each ad group, you're posting uh
text assets, image assets, and video
assets. And then the algorithm is just
figuring it out. Yes. Usually combining
some, you know, aspects of that. Usually
text is always with some component with
image or with video. But yeah, images
are used a lot. Also images are used
sometimes in the Play Store, too. So
again, on Android, you'll notice the
theme here. I talk a lot about the
differences between the two. But on
Android, I over-index for landscape
orientation images. I as of recent, I've
sort of taken this stance that I'm
aiming for like an 80/20 rule for
images. 80% of them on Android, I want
to be in landscape. And then I'll use
the remaining 20% for like square
portrait. Just because landscape always
gets more traffic. And Google also has
the option where you can like they have
the AI generator assets now where you
can actually like type in text and
create your own. One thing I tell people
is like you don't have to have a fully
designed image asset because Google
overlays so much within your asset. So
they're going to pull in your app icon.
They will in most cases pull in install
button. It says like close or install a
lot of times. And then they even like
pull in a rating. A lot of times people
don't realize that your App Store rating
is pulled in to the actual asset, too.
So
if you have a fully designed image asset
with like a bunch of text and an image
and a call to action
and in your rating if you're calling
that out for whatever reason, it's
really redundant. Google's already doing
it. So I usually tell people like use a
stock image.
They work just as well a lot of times.
They're free. You can just search for
them right as you're creating your ad
groups.
And um grab grab a few of those and see
what works. You don't have to I mean,
you can test it. You can And by test, I
mean putting something else in there and
seeing if it gets traffic. You can't run
like an AB test on an image asset. So
you got to just kind of like, you know,
throw it up there and see if it sticks.
So then the the recommendation here then
is like you don't like hire a graphic
designer and have this polished like
what you would typically perceive as an
image ad. Like you said with like a
clear call to action, a subtext
highlighting your favorite feature or
whatever. It's like the the assets
should the image assets should just be
very kind of plain. No text at all or
minimal text or like Again, it's not
like a hard and fast rule. I haven't
seen those the ones that are fully
designed, at least for the accounts that
I work on and a lot of my clients, I
haven't seen them get as much volume as
the ones that are just
images. And again, the whole concept is
because it's already overlaid anyway. So
in a lot of cases, if you're finding
that those aren't working for you or
they're not, you know, like the the
click-through rate's really low, then
sure, go ahead and design a fully. But I
I don't think you necessarily need that
in order to get started. How do you look
at the performance or can you even look
at the performance of individual assets
in UAC? Yes, you can. But I think
there's the difference. A lot of when I
was working at Google and working with a
lot of games, they would get really
frustrated that they couldn't see what
the combination of assets produced. So
like they wanted to be able to see,
"Okay, well, did this specific text plus
this image perform better than this text
with the same image?"
Google will not let you do that. They're
not showing you that level of
granularity. But you absolutely can see
like, "Hey, is this text asset
performing better than another text
asset?" And so you can break it down
quite a bit. There's actually a
performance rating in Google. If you
pull up your account, it will tell you
Google has a performance rating how your
asset is. Was it like best, good, low,
and then like learning. Just don't pay
attention to it.
I was joking. So I'm like, it's five
columns that you can't remove. They
serve almost no purpose, at least when
I'm optimizing an account. And the
reason why is that that performance
rating is based on the scale of the
campaign and the click-through rate, so
the engagement. So it's kind of like how
much can Google serve this asset and
then that's what the rating is based on.
Not necessarily how it's performing.
Performing, right? Like your actual
metric that you want to optimize
towards. So if you're new and that's how
you're approaching it, just go ahead and
ignore that. Focus on whatever you're
optimizing for, your CPI or your CPA.
How do you actually look at the
performance of it? So yeah, you you
know, you do the asset reporting. I pay
a lot of attention to where traffic is
serving. So talked a lot about like all
the different inventory types. So a lot
of times if I'm like, well, why is this
ad group performing, you know, worse
than this one or vice versa? A lot of
times I'll pull in the field, there's a
way to segment it so I can actually see
the percentage of traffic that's flowing
to search versus display or YouTube. And
that to me is a really helpful tool. It
guides me to understand like what might
be happening here. I also, well, Google
doesn't like it you might have to create
it as a custom column. I actually spend
a lot of time looking at CPMs. I don't
know if other people do that quite as
much, but I notice some big differences.
Again, like I'm you have to do some
guessing work on what's happening here
cuz not all of it is exposed. So a lot
of times if I notice like a big decline
in performance, then I check out, okay,
well, was there also a decline in CPM? A
lot of times cheaper CPMs mean worse
traffic, not always, but a lot of times.
So that's another thing that I pay
attention to when I'm going through and
actually like optimizing and for
performance. Are there any gotchas to
all of this as far as any ways to kind
of point the algorithm in specific
directions? You know, I I've heard folks
and of course you would never say this,
but I've heard folks say that, you know,
Google is going to optimize toward the
things that make them the most money and
so kind of to your point about like
looking at CPMs, if you're getting like
lower CPMs, it may be that it's being
served to lower quality traffic and
they're they're hitting your budget and
you're still getting the performance you
want, but maybe you could be getting
better performance. How do you think
about that? Yeah, you have to pay
attention to it. One of the things that
people again don't like when Google
rolled out UAC is that it blended a lot
of the traffic. And so all of a sudden
you have your highest like they can
serve at the highest performing traffic.
They know that that's going to convert
and then they serve the crappy stuff and
it all averages out and people are like,
well, I don't want the crap, you know, I
just want the premium stuff. And so you
do have to be on top of it. Those are
the sig like I was mentioning like the
CPMs, where your traffic is serving. You
can to some degree see what sites or
apps your ads are serving in or what
YouTube videos they're serving in. So I
pay attention to that sometimes like if
if it's a significant volume and I'm
like, well, this is just a crap site.
Like it's super spammy. There's like no
40 ads on there. I don't want my clients
to be included in that type of
inventory, but
And so you can actually go in there and
say like, don't show on this site
specifically or or you would even just
say, don't show in this type of
inventory? No, not on this type of
inventory. Although I think you can do
it for certain apps, but it does block
it at an account level. Not just at a
campaign level, but that doesn't usually
cause too much issue. But yeah, so
that's a reality. You do have to sort of
make sure that you're staying on top of
it. I know a lot of people are like, oh,
you just like, you know, set it and
forget it and it keeps doing it. It's
like, yes, if you're okay with that. If
you're okay knowing that you're getting
some of the crap and you can't avoid the
crap altogether, but you can try and
minimize it or try and increase the the
high quality stuff. And would you also
then be
looking at certain like images or text
that's hitting those lower CPMs that are
kind of giving you a hint that maybe
it's lower quality traffic and actually
just remove those assets from the ad
group? Is that how you would kind of
approach that? I did it yesterday for
one of my clients. Like this one's a
little bit tricky that I find is like in
this particular case they were getting a
lot of traffic from certain videos and
that was fueling the majority of their
scale. Like that's where all of the
volume was coming from. So initially I
was really resistant to just being like,
can them, you know, get rid of it.
Because then what can happen is that
that will tank the whole campaign. All
of a sudden it's like we've got no
conversions and so it's just like we'll
just die out. So you have to sometimes
be delicate with that. It's like a a
balance between how much you're removing
at once. And so in that case I kind of I
went in cautiously. I was like, okay, I
see these videos. Yeah, they're they
have a super high CPA. Sometimes also
important to like look at your even
further down funnel metrics. Like maybe
the CPA's okay, it's within target, but
in this particular case the ROAS was
crap. Then I had to make the call and so
I just slowly started kind of removing
those assets so that it didn't cause the
campaign to just have no conversions and
then give it a week and then after that
I got to pull them all because Google's
trying to get away with something.
Gotcha.
So we talked about structuring campaigns
early on and then kind of that first
like just just launch with one app
campaign
and then, you know, do your testing in
in four or five
ad groups. How do you scale that up or
like what are your kind of campaign
structuring and testing? When do you
layer on more campaigns? How do you do
that smartly? Well, layering on more
campaigns I think in any specific geo,
maybe you don't want to do it. Although
it can be a hack sometimes. I've noticed
some people where they're like, I'm not
getting enough scale. Like even though,
you know, I've seen people with budgets
of like, you know, a hundred thousand
dollars a day and just because they want
to signal to the system like spend my
money and it won't sometimes. So
one hack, this is definitely not a
Google best practice, but it's something
I think I've learned more so like as a
practitioner doing this all the time.
Sometimes just like duplicating the
campaigns for whatever reason like you
duplicate it and that signal to Google
is like, oh, we have something new to go
out and we have to go test it. And so
then you might start to see more scale
whereas that existing campaign had just
kind of remained very steady. So that's
like one hacky way to do it. But again,
like the the scaling piece is like it's
just sort of slow and steady. I
think it's hard if you're reaching your
max capacity in one market to really
force more scale without getting really
aggressive with your bids.
So then I start to look at other markets
that might perform well. And then what
about ad groups? Who are you constantly
like adding or removing ad groups? As
you said like if you're targeting
specific kind of messaging or, you know,
talking about specific features. Are you
are is that an area that you're you
actively test like add a new ad group
more focused on this feature versus that
feature and remove that ad group that
wasn't performing?
Yeah, so um a lot of times what you'll
find though is that they won't the new
ones that you add in. Like for whatever
reason Google favors like their first
child. So like the
the first ad group that you create, it I
just seen it happen so many times. That
is the one that they're like, we're
we're running with this one. Even if
another one that seems to be performing
better, it doesn't always get as much
scale. So yes, I do add in new ad
groups. Like, you know, around the
holidays for example, if we're testing a
new holiday theme. I put it in in a
specific ad group. That also makes it
easier to manage, right? Like I don't
forget about it later on that like, oh,
we're running like Halloween creatives.
Like that's labeled separately. It
wasn't mixed in with a bunch of others.
So like I can just pull up that ad
group. If there's something seasonal
that's going on, like, you know, I work
with some apps where
natural disasters for example that
happen, that's when they see spikes in
their traffic and so we run individual
like natural
disaster ad groups. Like if a
hurricane's happening or a tornado or,
you know, if it's avalanche season or
whatever, we have those separate and
test out those things. So yes, I am
constantly going in and and trying new
ones, but
a lot of times they won't get meaningful
volume to really be able to say like was
it worth it? So you might have to leave
them on for a little bit longer. And
then with that kind of first child as
you called it, the the kind of one ad
group that the app campaign kind of
preferences, would you then start to
expand the assets in that ad group as
kind of an experimentation of adding
some new themes and other stuff in that
high performing ad group?
Yeah, I mean I think a lot of times I
try and just what I've noticed, I don't
hear people talk about it as often. I so
prior to Google I worked at Pandora and
that was more like a brands plays. And
one thing we talked a lot more about
there, keep in mind this is a really
long time ago, but was ad fatigue. And I
don't think that we talk about that
quite as much and I mean maybe we do in
the UA space, but I think that's
something that people need to realize is
that even in those high performing ad
groups, right? At some point people are
just tired of seeing the same thing over
and over. It's just hit the same
audience too many times and they've
tuned it out. And so
or Google's just gotten in this like
habit of like showing it to the same
like on the same inventory or to the
same people. So even making a small tiny
adjustment actually like if you had
something that said like, buy it today
and you changed it to buy today, you
took out the it, that sends Google into
a whole new learning. It's like, we have
to figure it out. So it's not a new
concept, but to Google it is.
And so, it'll go out and test something
new and and, you know, the ad isn't
fatigued quite as much. So, we've kind
of weaved it into this entire
conversation, but any other kind of
troubleshooting or analysis tips on
like, you know, if things aren't
performing well, like these are the
first places to look and like how do how
do you troubleshoot campaigns and and
budget and and things to to get optimal
performance? I mean, I guess that's why
people bring me on is like that's what I
spend a lot of my time doing. It's what
my team does as well. The people that
actually like know the platform pretty
well, I don't think this comes as any
surprise. Everybody uses that the
segment called like networks.
And that's again where you can see at an
asset level how your ads are serving
across all those different inventory
sources. That is so important. You
really need to understand where those
ads are serving and, you know, I again,
I didn't audit for somebody just this
week and they were like, well, we don't
understand like why we're getting kind
of this crap traffic. And I'm like, it's
because all of these assets are serving
on the display network.
And you're not getting any of that
high-quality search traffic. And so, if
you don't know to look at something like
that, then you're like, oh, Google's
just not working. So, now we you know,
have to go back and figure out ways. How
do you force it in some ways to spend in
these other areas or test this other
areas. I guess my big tip for people is
like, don't just assume that it is doing
what you think it should be doing.
Sometimes it'll go rogue on you. And so,
you do have to kind of know how to
manage it. And also, what metrics
matter. Like I said,
I pay a lot of attention to CPMs. I know
a lot of other people will pay attention
to like IPMs. I don't tend to pay
attention to that as much because of the
like we talked about it extensively, the
network changes. So, your IPM on search
is going to be really different than
your IPM on display. So,
I think that's kind of unfair to hold
them to the same bar. Anyway, so, I I
tend to look at those other like early
metrics to determine if something
ultimately is going to perform well or
why maybe it is or isn't performing
well. Sounds like it's a a trust, but
verify situation where to use UAC, you
have to trust the algorithm cuz it's
like you you you just can't get around
having to trust that it's going to get
you performance, but then you verify
that it's actually giving you the
performance you want. And then kind of
subtly nudging it different directions
with all these techniques that we've
been talking about. Absolutely. That
might be my new tag. Trust, but verify.
Trust, but verify. Yeah. Any
subscription app specific
considerations? So, you know, most of
our audience is subscription app
practitioners as opposed to, you know,
games. So, there anything with like, you
know, free trial optimization, you know,
targeting the install versus a trial
versus the conversion, any kind of
subscription app specific tips? I I
don't think that this is unique for
Google, but maybe just if if somebody's
starting out to understand what goes
into this. I typically don't like people
to optimize their their campaigns for
purchases
or like, you know, trial complete or
something like that because those tend
to happen way too far out, right? Those,
you know, if you're a 7-day trial, I
think most subscriptions are.
For Google to get that data back 7 days
later is just too much of a lag. And so,
really optimizing for those like earlier
signals most of the time is a start
trial in most cases. Um, but you can
play around with different events to
optimize for. So, I think, yeah, for for
the subscription apps, that's probably
the piece that I would pay most
attention to. The other thing I'm
getting a lot of questions on and I'll
be totally honest, I don't have a super
sound opinion just yet. I noticed that
Google, I know Google is pushing their
value-based bidding. So, this is tROAS,
that's what most people refer to it as.
And I think it's still TBD if it really
works for subscription apps. It wasn't
designed for subscription apps, right?
It's really designed for IAPs. And then
they have another product that's
designed for ad-monetized apps.
Same name, still tROAS. But I think with
with subscription apps, they've had sort
of like a 50/50 hit rate on whether or
not that bid type can work for their
business model.
So, for that one, if you're feeling like
you're being pushed at all on it, I
think it's okay to be skeptical, but at
the same time, it has worked for some
folks, so it might be worth a short
test. Yeah. And speaking of being
pushed, I know one of the questions a
lot of people would be asking,
shouting into the car as they're driving
listening to the podcast or otherwise,
would be, you know, you worked at
Google. How do we get in touch with
Google? How do I get a campaign manager?
How do I work with Google? And then you
already mentioned one and I know you've
mentioned others in the past that that a
good account manager can actually get
you some data that you wouldn't get
otherwise. So, It's the easy answer, but
it's also the honest one. You got to
spend more. You have to think about it,
right? Like, I don't know if people
don't get mad about that. It's like,
Google has to pay these people, right?
And so, they have to make sure that
they're getting an ROI on these
individuals. So, if you're spending 200
bucks a month and you're like, well, I
want to scale. It's like, they need to
see proof in that. They're not going
with the trust and verify
mentality. They're like, no, we need we
need hard evidence that you can pay
this. You got the budget for it. And
then we're going to give you the
support. You know, we're paying these
people X amount of money. Like we got to
make sure it's worth it for us. So, that
that's really how you get it. The one
thing I would call out though is that
like your
that depends on your market. And
ultimately you get assigned based on
your billing country that you have set
up in your Google Ads account. And so,
like I have a client, he's based in the
US, but his account is billed out of the
UK. So, his rep sits in Dublin. So,
there's different like spend criteria.
Obviously, in the US, they're going to
have like the highest thresholds. You
got to be spending a decent amount in
order to get support. But if you're in a
smaller market, like let's call it
Vietnam, you know, that threshold might
not be as high. Is it a we'll call you,
don't call us kind of situation? Like
once you start spending enough, they
reach out to you or or how how does that
kind of first contact work? Yes, that is
the case. They they will reach out to
you. And typically, you'll if you're
wondering like, well, is today the day
that they're going to reach out to me?
No, it happens on a quarterly basis. All
of these things happen
um, call them like book refreshes,
right? This is when the the reps
actually like they have their assigned
book of accounts that they work with and
their goals against. Yes, they have
revenue goals. So, they will be pushing
you to spend more money. And those get
changed out. You rarely can you make a
mix-up in the middle of a quarter. And
so, if you're wondering, hey, is like,
am I going to be able to talk with
somebody and it's May, right? April,
May, June, that's that's Q2. No, you
might not hear from somebody until July
if you think that you are spending
significant amount. But I would say once
you get a rep,
I I feel like people underutilize them
sometimes. Maybe my Google folks are
going to get mad at me. They're like,
oh, no, like, you know, we're we're
bombarded with requests. But I think
that if you're smart, like ask for more.
Ask for more information. Be specific.
They have a lot of it. They can't always
share, you know, everything that you
might want to see, but I think that a
lot of times people don't realize like
how much they do have and that they can
share.
Um, so, make those asks. For people
before Google reaches out, are there any
like support channels or is there
um, like a form they can fill out that
that is actually helpful or or do those
just kind of get routed to people who
can't really help you anyway? When
you're reaching out, those are all going
to go to vendor teams. And that's not to
say that they're not helpful sometimes.
I I haven't found them to be as helpful
most of the time.
And so, oh, I don't have a great answer.
I mean, like, send me a message if you
really have a, you know, a question that
you're like, I can't figure this out for
myself, but that's kind of the best bet
at that point.
Yeah, it makes sense. And like you said,
and you know, this has been a long time
frustration of developers working with
Apple as well as Google that like, ah, I
can't talk to anybody. Well, yeah,
because anybody that you would talk to
who could make a decision is being paid,
you know, total compensation probably
$300,000
that it costs Apple to have that
employee to be able to talk to you. And
so, it makes sense. Like you said, it's
like, they they have to strategically
allocate those resources in a way that's
going to give them a return on
investment. Like this is not a
you know, these are for-profit companies
who are beholden to their shareholders
and optimizing towards shareholders, not
you as an indie developer or even as a
large developer. You know, that's
something I've kind of come to
internalize a little bit more in these
last few years is like, okay, yeah,
Apple's not like my friend. They're
fiduciary as their shareholders. When
you kind of really internalize that and
you look at all these decisions and the
way they do things and, you know, them
pushing so hard on on collecting their
fees and like all those kind of things,
it's like,
that's just how the world works. It's
just how it works.
Yes. Actually, the ads team at Google is
pretty substantial. Like from what I've
heard, Meta's made some like major cuts
on their support like to the point that
like nobody has a rep anymore at Meta.
I'm exaggerating, but like not, you know
what I mean? Like there's not a lot of
support there. Google's ads team, I
think, is still pretty healthy as it
stands today. So, I mean, I feel like a
lot of people do have a rep, even if
it's somebody By the way, there's
different tiers of reps, right? Like
based on your spend. So, there is a
difference in support level, but I think
maybe even more frustrating is on the
play side of things.
Where that team is actually really,
really lean.
And so, I feel like nobody has support
from play. And then also you have to
think about it. Like on ads, they're
like, "As long as you're spending money
with us, great." Play only cares if
you're making money for them, right? So,
if you're heavy on ad- ad-funded, they
don't care. They're not making any money
on you, right? Like, yeah, you could be
a massive app that has, you know, 100
million downloads or whatever. You're
not making any money for play, so they
don't, you know, they're not as
concerned. But that that team is
actually incredibly small, and so
there's not a lot of developers. And I
think they I'm not trying to say they
favor them, but again, if you're
thinking about how these companies make
money,
they work with a lot of the gaming
studios.
That's where a lot of their support
flows. Yeah, it just makes sense. But, I
will say that if you're struggling with
these things, this is why you created
Candid Consulting.
Um so, how can people reach out? Are you
accepting new clients?
Yes, please reach out if if you're
interested in talking. I think And I do
I have sort of an agency side of the
business where I actually do all of this
for my clients, but I find that a lot of
people do reach out just hoping to like
get some information, so I do partner
with people in that capacity, too. You
can reach out to me on LinkedIn. My
name's Ashley Black. You There's not too
many of us. You should be able to find
me. Or you can reach out directly
through the website, which is
candidconsultinggroup.com.
And yeah, I'm happy to chat with people.
I'm always interested to learn what
other people are working on, what
problems people are seeing, and a lot of
times people just want to know like what
actually is going on at Google, like,
you know,
shed some light or like lift the curtain
a little bit. And so, that's always fun
to talk about, too. Well, it's been so
fascinating and and fun to get the kind
of inside scoop on a lot of this stuff,
but then also like now that you've been
out of Google for over a year and worked
with so many different clients. Like so
many of these insights are are things
you probably didn't even know when you
were inside Google. And you've done a
lot of testing, as we've talked about.
And so, thank you so much for being so
open to share your experiences and how
you optimize all this. Absolutely. I
appreciate you having me.
Thanks so much for listening.
If you have a minute, please leave a
review in your favorite podcast player.
You can also stop by chat.subclub.com
to join our private community.